

Zaryab Javed

Date of birth: 15/09/1999

Nationality: Pakistani

Gender: Male

CONTACT

Yasir Street House No
CB1074 Near Qasim Market
Rawalpindi,
46000 Rawalpindi, Pakistan
(Home)



zaryabjaved06@gmail.com



(+92) 3008369857

ABOUT ME

I am a Software Engineer. Reliable Quality Assurance Analyst worked in different projects during my career to ensure the highest quality outcomes possible and always been an ambitious person, have never been satisfied with my performance and every time I want to do better. I always get mesmerized by the areas of Quality Assurance, Manual testing and want to work as a professional in these fields

WORK EXPERIENCE

09/07/2020 - 09/09/2020 Rawalpindi, Pakistan

Internship IntraSols

This was an internship program offered by Well Known Software House i.e., IntraSols. During this program I worked on Front End Design and Did a Blackbox testing.

This whole program was based on developing knowledge among the internees that how this technology works and why its being adapted by many organizations.

At the end of this internship program we developed clone apps which are already available on the application stores .

07/03/2022 - CURRENT Islamabad, Pakistan

Senior Quality Assurance Analyst WeRPlay

Proficient in game testing across multiple platforms, including consoles. Experienced in adhering to Microsoft's certification test cases for ensuring quality standards on console platforms During this period, I have undertaken multiple projects and gained experience in the following areas:

- Performed various tests as per the required client standards
- Remarkable experience in performing tests on various games/ applications and identifying all glitches Immense knowledge of various bug logging tools.
- Solid understanding of performing tests on multiple platforms. I have contributed to various projects, including:

1. **Marvels Snap**: MARVEL SNAP is a fast-paced collectible card game with innovative mechanics that has won multiple Game of the Year Awards. A project by NuVerse, HONGKONG

- 2. **Lost Twins 2**: Lost Twins 2 is an incredibly cute puzzle adventure that will challenge, entertain and maybe even inspire you. Guide Abi and Ben on their journey as they move across platforms, engage in challenging puzzles, swap tiles to create paths and overcome obstacles to reunite and find their way back home.
- 3. **Jambro**: A music application by JAMBRO PTE LTD, Singapore. Its like TikTok for music artists where users can upload their Jams to show skills and art.
- 4. **Explottens:** Explottens is a heart pumping, hair raising, pawtastic shoot 'em up that follows K.I.T the pilot and his band of misfits as they zip, boost, and shoot through the sky, battling the ferocious felines known as K.L.A.W! Dominate the skies and battle your way through an army of evil cats.
- 5. **Knight's Edge:** Knight's Edge is a strategy game where you'll have a great time joining the main character on his mission to advance through as many settings as possible, for which he will have to defeat all the enemies that try to stop him. Knight's Edge is a multiplayer game by LIGHT FOX GAMES, USA
- Spades Plus: A Classic strategic Card game By Zynga Games, USA

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

13/09/2017 - 09/08/2021 Islamabad, Pakistan

BS Software Engineering Capital University Of Science And Technology

Address Islamabad Expressway, Kahuta, Road Zone-V Sihala, Islamabad, Islamabad Capital Territory, Islamabad, Islamabad, Pakistan | **Website** www.cust.edu.pk

15/08/2015 - 13/08/2017 Rawalpindi, Pakistan

ICS Punjab Group Of Colleges

Address Branch 82A Near Iran Embassy Rehmanabad Rawalpindi, 46000, Rawalpindi, Pakistan

LANGUAGE SKILLS

MOTHER TONGUE(S): Urdu

Other language(s):

English

Listening B2Spoken production B1Reading B2Spoken interaction B1

Writing B2

Seraiki

Listening B1Spoken production B1Reading B1Spoken interaction B1Writing B1

Pashto

Listening B2Spoken production B1Reading A1Spoken interaction B2

Writing A1

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

PROJECTS

19/09/2020 - 08/08/2021

Cardiac Disease Detection System

This is the project that we are working on as our Final Year Project. As the name suggests this is basically a disease detection system, which will assist the doctors in their decision making and Give them a second opinion. The system is based on machine learning techniques and algorithms. It provides results based on the concept of Binary Classification i.e., If the person possesses a cardiac disease or not.

HOBBIES AND INTERESTS

Sports

I like to stay fit and healthy and in order to do so I have always been passionate about sports. I like participating in all the sports but out of all I enjoy Football, Table Tennis, Cricket, Snooker the most.

VOLUNTEERING

09/02/2021 - 30/03/2021 Islamabad

Volunteer Service

Alkhidmat Foundation, Islamabad Performed Volunteer service for AlKhidmat Foundation, Islamabad. This program lasted for about 8 weeks